



)+41 78 248 31 14



elvira.a.graf@gmail.com



elvira-graf.dev

# SKILLS

# AUSBILDUNG



### PROFIL

Erfahrener Experte aus dem Versicherungsbereich, der sich der Programmierung widmet. Abgeschlossener SheCodes Next Kurs, aktuell im CS50 Kurs an der Harvard University. Erfolgreicher Agenturpartner bei Allianz mit Ausbildung zur Versicherungsfachfrau bei Ergo. Lassen Sie uns meine vielfältigen Erfahrungen mit neuen technischen Fähigkeiten kombinieren!

### ARBEITSERFAHRUNG

### Agenturpartner (Allianz)

Allianz // Jan 2023 - Feb 2024

• Selbstständige Vertriebspartnerin bei der Allianz, spezialisiert auf Verkauf, Beratung und individuelle Versicherungslösungen

#### Agenturpartner (Ergo)

Ergo // Jan 2022 - Dez 2022

• spezialisiert auf Verkauf und Beratung für individuelle Versicherungslösungen

#### Vertriebsassistenz

Ergo // Jun 2021 - Dez 2021

 Verantwortlich f
ür die administrative Unterstützung des Vertriebsteams, Koordination von Terminen und Kommunikation mit Kunden

#### Inhaberin eines Gastronomiebetriebs

Newage Bar Memmingen // Mai 2017 - März 2018

• Verwaltung vom täglichen Betrieb, einschließlich Mitarbeiterführung, Kundenservice und Geschäftsentwicklung





+41 78 248 31 14



elvira.a.graf@gmail.com



elvira-graf.dev

# **SKILLS**

- Profound expertise in CSS, JavaScript,
   React.js, and Bootstrap, coupled with
   practical experience in SEO optimization.
- Proficient in using modern development tools such as VSCode, Git, GitHub, and various hosting services.
- Advanced understanding of UI/UX design principles and expertise in creating responsive web designs.
- Leadership skills and effective project management experience from the hospitality industry.
- Strong customer orientation and communication skills, proven in the insurance sector.
- Problem-solving abilities and adaptability developed through diverse professional challenges.

# **EDUCATION**

- CS50 Harvard
   (Introduction to Computer Science)
- Shecodes Next (Certified Career Developer)
- Certified Insurance Specialist (IHK)



## PROFILE

I'm a versatile professional transitioning from insurance expertise to the world of coding. I recently completed the SheCodes Next course am currently working through the CS50 course at Harvard University. Previously, I excelled as an agency partner at Allianz and completed my insurance specialist training at Ergo. Let's combine my diverse background with emerging tech skills!

# WORK EXPERIENCE

### **Agency Partner (Allianz)**

Allianz // Jan 2023 - Feb 2024

 Independent sales partner at Allianz, specializing in sales, consulting, and customized insurance solutions

#### **Agency Partner (Ergo)**

Ergo // Jan 2022 - Dec 2022

 In charge of administering support to the sales team by scheduling appointments and liaising with customers

# **Insurance Sales Support Representative**

Ergo // Jun 2021 - Dec 2021

 Responsible for providing administrative support to the sales team, coordinating appointments, and communicating with customers

#### **Entrepreneur in the Hospitality Industry**

Newage Bar Memmingen // May 2017 - Mar 2018

 Management of daily operations, including staff supervision, customer service, and business development